{"data":[{"question":"The main office of the factory can be found in Maple Street in New York City.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The main","b":"the","c":"be found","d":"in","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- In-> on","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Because there are less members present tonight than there were last night, we must wait until the next meeting to vote.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"less","b":"than","c":"were","d":"to vote","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Less-> more","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"David is particularly fond of cooking, and he often cooks really delicious meals.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"particularly","b":"fond of","c":"often cooks","d":"really","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\nReally -> Very or extremely (Really is especially frequent in spoken English. In writing, people usually prefer to use very or extremely to emphasize an adjective, or very much to emphasize a verb)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The progress made in space travel for the early 1960s is remarkable.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"progress","b":"made","c":"in space","d":"for","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- For-> in","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Sandra has not rarely missed a play or concert since she was seventeen years old.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"not rarely","b":"a play","c":"since","d":"was seventeen years old","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Not rarely-> rarely","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The governor has not decided how to deal with the new problems already.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The","b":"has","c":"how to deal with","d":"already","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Already-> yet","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"There was a very interesting news on the radio this morning about the earthquake in Italy.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"There was","b":"a","c":"on the","d":"about","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- A-> the\/some","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The professor had already given the homework assignment when he had remembered that Monday was a holiday.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"the homework assignment","b":"had remembered","c":"Monday","d":"was","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Had remembered-> Remembered","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Having been beaten by the police for striking an officer, the man will cry out in pain.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"by","b":"for striking an officer","c":"the man","d":"will cry out","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Will cry out-> cried out","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"This table is not stable enough to support a television, and that one probably isn't neither.\n\u00a0","a":"not stable enough","b":"to support","c":"that one","d":"neither","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Neither-> either","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}